Viewers all over the world, Heaven is aware.
Viewers, wherever you are, whatever you are doing at this moment,
open your lips and ask Jesus, "Speak to me, Lord!"
Oh, Holy Spirit, speak to me, Lord.
Thank You, Lord.
Viewers all over the world, at this moment, whatever situation you are in,
distance is not a barrier.
Evil spirit, I break your dominion!
In the life of our children, our people all over the world, evil spirit, let your dominion be broken!
Let your dominion be broken!
Open your lips, right now - begin to break the dominion. Break his dominion!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You, evil spirit, your finger in the life of my people,
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Your point in the life of my people, be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Let your dominion be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Demon, let your dominion be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever chain, chain of poverty,
whatever chain, chain of sickness,
whatever chain, chain of setback,
whatever chain, chain of disappointment,
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Loose your grip!
Viewers, hear the clearance - visible and clear; this is the promise of God for you -
clearance of your health.
Affliction, wherever it is located, disease, wherever it is located, open your lips;
this is your time, to get you clear.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, get your health clear.
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Yes, if Jesus says you are free, you are free.
Believe it; confess your freedom.
Begin to confess your freedom.
Confess your freedom.
I am healed!
My kidney is healed; I am healed!
My liver is healed; I am healed!
My blood is healed; I am healed!
My bone is healed; I am healed!
My fluids are healed; I am healed!
My organ is healed; I am healed!
In the name of Jesus!
Confess your freedom. Confess your healing.
I am healed, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips; begin to confess your healing.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers, breakthrough in your finances, career, business!
Breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Can you hear what I am hearing?
I can hear, "Breakthrough!"
Breakthrough!
God bless you.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, wherever you are, here is clearance that you are free.
I say, this is clearance that you are free.
This is a message for you: This is clearance - you are free!
If God says you are free, who is man?
So, this is clearance, that you are free!
Where there is clearance, there is God.
Where there is clearance, there is light.
Here is clearance, in Jesus Christ's name!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name